BITCH YOU
BITCH YOU GUESSED IT
Still in that place
and I'm flexin'
HOO
BITCH YOU GUESSED IT
I'M STILL WITH MY [UH OH]s
come and test us
O.G.G.​
Bitch, you guessed it
Walkin' around with extra in my pockets
Bitch, you next to us
Why the fuck are you next to us?
Bitch, you should come test us
I seen what you rockin' and, bitch
You can't dress with us
Seen what yo' bitch looked like
And, [UH OH], I wasn't impressed or nothin'
Fuck-[UH OH], come and talk it out
Fuck-[UH OH], we ain't talkin' it out
What the fuck we finna talk about?
All we know is that Mula, Benjis, Franklins
And that Guala, Fetti with us
Bunch of young [UH OH]s
Bunch of them bitches, all in they whip
Lickin' on tit
Runnin' my check up, I think I'm with Nike, I'm sprintin'
Sheesh, y'all couldn't hear me?
Bitch, you guessed it
You was motherfuckin' right
HOO
Still with my [UH OH]s and we flexin'
Hoo
Bitch, you guessed it
BITCH, YOU GUESSED IT
HOO
You was right
Still on my [UH OH]s and we flexin'
Hoo
Bitch, you guessed it